鸣潮_今汐

created by 鸣潮/1010浣

----------------禁止事项/Forbidden---------------

■二次配布
  再配布したりする
  Redistribution 

■商业使用以及任何涉及到金钱交易的使用
  商業利用および金銭取引に関わるあらゆる使用
  Commercial use

■涉及R18（色情、血腥、暴力……）、政治、宗教、违反法律的使用
  R18（エロ、血、暴力……）政治、宗教、犯罪の使用
  R-18 (porn, blood, violence...), political, religious , crime use

■侮辱他人或国家的使用
  他者や他国を侮蔑するための利用
  Contempt towards other countries or people

■违反公共秩序与善良风俗、明智、健全的判断力的使用
  公序良俗、良識に反する使用
  Violating public and order, lack of wise and subtle judgment.  

■欺瞒作者的信息或谎称自己为原作者
  このデータの製作者を騙ること
  Deceiving/Claiming to be the original creator

-----------改造&再配布/Edit and Redistribution-----------

■允许改造，但是不可以改造为其他角色，模型不论改造与否禁止二次配布
  改造OKです, 但し、このモデルの一部を別モデルに移植不可。再配布禁止。
  Allowed to edit ,but  it can't be edit out of the character.Anyway,Redistribution is not allowed.
 
---------------免责/Disclaimer---------------

请自觉遵守相关规则，本文件使用过程中所发生的一切问题，本人和素材作者不承担任何责任
このデータを使用したことにより何らかのトラブルが発生した場合でも、当方と素材の作者は一切の責任を負わない
The editor of this model data and the autors of parts are not responsible for any damage caused by using this model

本模型素材的最终版权归【广州库洛科技有限公司】所有
このモデル材料の最終著作権は、【広州庫洛科技有限公司】に属します
The final copyright of this model material belongs to Guangzhou Kuluo Technology Co., Ltd

created by 鸣潮/1010浣